

EMAIL: MVPBREMAH@GMAIL.COM

MVPBREMAH@YAHOO.COM

CELL: 781 492 2173 HOME: 781 420 0536

WEBSITE: HTTPS://BREMAH-MVP.GITHUB.IO/REACT-PORTFOLIO/

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER / IT SPECIALIST

My name is Bremah, A full stack web developer and graduated from the university of New Hampshire. I am now proficient in React, Angular, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express, HTML & CSS, i should say front and backend

Am well equipped for designing front-end and a logical brain for tackling back-end, I'd be an essential asset to your team and ready to battle.

Aside from programing am also an Information technology specialist with a bachelor's degree in information technology

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP, JQUERY, API, NODE JS, ANGULAR, MYSQL CISCO/ CNA, COMPUTER OPERATIONS, TECHNICAL SUPPORT, DESKTOP SUPPORT, HARDWARE AND SOFTWARE SUPPORT, TROUBLESHOOTING, NETWORKING. REMOTE ACCESS, CYBER AND COMPUTER SECURITY.

EXPERIENCE

INMOTION ENTERTAINMENT

IT TECHNICIAN / SPECIALIST

AUGUST 2019 - PRESENT, EAST BOSTON LOGAN AIRPORT

INMOTIONS ENTERTAINMENT is the leading electronics company that delivers products and services to clients on all major airports in the United States of America. Including all latest electronics from major companies like BOSE Headphones, IPADS from APPLE among others.

ROLES:

Provide support to clients.

Ensure that computer hardware and software, as well as network and server work consistently and correctly.

Install new software and program.

configure network and databases

provide assistance to end users.

Troubleshooting systems and software.

Manage systems and information security

customer support. among others.

MASTERS ELECTRONICS / IT SPECIALIST

JAN 2014 - JAN 2018, KAMPALA, UGANDA

MASTERS ELECTRONICS was the leading dealer in all local and imported electronics like musical gadgets like, guitars, pianos, speakers, amplifiers, crossovers, microphones, and all the latest sound systems.

Roles:

Install and configure network, manage database, provide user support, manage information security, troubleshooting systems and software. Among others.

Other PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Immersive, 2020 - Present

Developed several mobile first web-applications and built several user-friendly websites including my react portfolio using React.js, JavaScript, and several other programming languages, libraries, and frameworks for-example react, angular, bootstrap, JavaScript, html, css, node among others.

Noted projects

-Created an interactive Connect Chore app that helps users manage household chores hence maintain proper hygiene in a home; used HTML, CSS, and JS React.

-Created an interactive Geo-battle application where users can create their own customized player who can then battle Florida Man villain. The user will attempt to score the most points and compare their score to their friends to see who the best Geo-battler is! In the app, users will be given a set amount of point and must choose wisely how to creat their player.

-I have also collaborated with several other senior software engineer assisting them throughout multiple projects as a freelancer while working my way to a successfully developing my skills as a software engineer.

Checkout my GitHub for more about my projects https://github.com/Bremah-mvp

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF NEW HAMPSHIRE

CERTIFICATE IN FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

JAN 2020 – DEC 2020 NEW HAMPSHIRE

GRADUATED FROM UNIVERSITY OF NEW HAMPSHIRE CODING BOOTCAMP LEARNING SOFTWARE AND WEB DEVELOPMENT. And was rewarded with a full stack web development certificate after emerging as an A student throughout the entire course.

MAKERERE UNIVERSITY

BACHELOR'S IN SCIENCE AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

JAN 2009 - DEC 2013, KAMPALA /UGANDA

I attained a bachelor's in science and information technology.

CGP = 4.00 Overall CGPA = 4.50

AWARDS AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

- BACHELOR'S IN SCIENCE AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY
- CISCO CCNA CERTIFICATION
- TWO TIMES EMPLOYEES OF THE YEAR (MASTERS ELECTRONICS)
- OUTSTANDING EMPLOYEE AT INMOTION ENT.
- Full stack web development certificate.